Hello, today in this video we will learn
about the best four term insurance plan offering companies in India in 2022. But before starting the video,
one important thing is that if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then subscribe so that
you get the right information at the right time.
Now I would
like to introduce myself. My name is
Kajal. I keep giving you health and life insurance
duty updates through this channel
and also give you advice on every insurance related
problem. Our
team has 12 years of experience in the insurance industry
and we
also provide consultancy related to claims. Let's
start today's video. Friends,
while buying term insurance, a question
definitely comes to our mind that we are
paying the premium of term insurance, but after 40 to 50
years, when the time
comes to take our claim, what will happen if the company from which we are buying the term plan closes down.
This fear remains in everyone's mind, which is
absolutely right. But the premium we
pay to the company is our hard earned money
and the security of our family for life.
If that  If the money goes down the drain, the
family could be left stranded. Now, it's clear
that you need to
connect with a reliable company to buy a term plan.
We'll tell you about those companies in the next video. The
video is going to be informational,
so be sure to watch this video until the end.
First, we'll give you some basic knowledge about the
common benefits a good company
offers in its plan. The
inbuilt benefits offered
are add-on covers, which you
can purchase separately by paying a small extra premium.
Secondly, you can also take riders. There are
some add-ons and riders we'd recommend. The
first is premium
waiver. This rider benefits you when
you develop a permanent disability. By
purchasing this rider, your annual
premium is waived, and your
policy remains active for the life of the policy. The
second is critical illness treatment. If
you develop a serious illness like cancer, heart attack, or heart stroke,
you'll be given a lump sum amount for its treatment. The
third benefit is life stage
benefit. This means you can choose your insurance.  You can increase
your insurance cover at any stage of life. If
your family members are increasing,
you can also add them to this policy. The
fourth benefit is accidental death
benefit. If the insured person dies due to an
accident during the policy term,
you
get accidental death benefit. These are some of the benefits
that are common in a good company's term plan.
If you don't get these benefits from any company, then
you should not choose that company's term
plan. Let's move ahead
in this video and tell you
which company's term plan is best for you.
If you are going to buy a term plan in 2024, then
you can invest in these companies. The
first company
is ADAC, which provides you with high coverage at a low premium.
This company is known as
a trusted company in the Indian market.
Its claim solvency
ratio is very good. This company's term
insurance plan has two riders.
Its options are Accidental
Disability Rider, Income Benefit Rider,
ADFC Life Critical  Illness Rider:
You get personal accident cover here. You also get 100%
accidental death cover. You also get
cancer cover here.
If the insured person is diagnosed with cancer at any stage during the policy term, the
company will provide you with money for cancer treatment.
Apart from this, ADAC company also gives you the option of a large sum assured ranging
from a minimum of ₹5 lakh to a maximum of ₹10 crore.
Another
company is ICICI. This company is famous
for offering high-coverage term plans at affordable premiums, in which you also
get the option to increase your life cover. This company
provides critical illness cover. You
also get tax benefits here.
This company also provides benefits in case of permanent disability.
You will get financial security here, in which
in case of accidental death of the insured person, the
company will pay up to ₹2 crore to your family members.
For example, if your
term insurance cover is ₹1 crore, then
in case of accidental death,
your family will receive ₹1 crore from the company under the Accidental Death Rider Benefit.  The
reason is that we want to recommend this
company to you by placing it in the category of best companies.
Now the third
company is Max Life.
Buying a term plan from this Max Life Insurance Company provides
you with many benefits. First,
your family gets financial
protection against uncertainties. Second, you are
covered for a maximum of 75 years under this company. Third, your dependents
get unlimited benefits. By
purchasing a term plan from this company, your dependents
get relief from loans or debt.
This plan provides you financial security in case of disability.
Last but not the
least, Max Life Insurance Company
provides you with various options for affordable premiums and discounts.
You get many premium payment options here, in
which you can pay the premium as per your convenience.
Riders are available for extra benefits.
That is why we have placed Max Life Insurance Company
's term plans in the best term plan
category. You can move forward with these
and make a secure investment.
Now, the last company we will
recommend to you is TA AIA Life
Insurance.  This company
offers a high-risk cover plan at an affordable premium.
This company
provides coverage that exceeds the premium paid for the policy,
which will meet your family's financial needs after your death. The amount
received through this company's term plan is
sufficient for you in case of a medical emergency or illness. This
company's term plan
provides complete coverage up to 100 years of age, ensuring
your family's security throughout your life.
This company's plan
also offers optional riders and add-on covers,
which you can combine with the term plan to
benefit from serious illnesses, unexpected medical emergencies, and hospitalization expenses. You
can definitely choose this company's term plan; it will be
a very smart decision. So, friends, that's all for
today's video. We hope
you found the information in this video truly
beneficial. We will continue to
bring you important information related to health and life insurance. To all those who are
connected with us, please
continue on this journey with us. If you are
new to our channel, please
subscribe to our channel and
thank you.